(自来也)大蛇丸。
Orochimaru…
なんだかね イテテッ。
I wonder what that was?
ネコちゃんがチョロチョロしてたと
思ったけどね…。
I thought it was a kitty
scuttling about, oh well…
BATHS
Oh!
お～ いい眺めだのぉ～。
What a sight!
(自来也)オッパイ いっぱい…。
Boobs.
Lots of boobs.
いい気分！
This is great!
(大蛇丸)わざわざ呼ぶから
何かと思ったら…。
Is this what you called me out for?
僕はもう帰る。
おい おい 声がでかいのぉ。
I'm leaving.
Hey…
Don't talk so loud.
ヘヘッ お前も見るか？
You want a look?
お～ お尻もいっぱいだってえの。
Oh, lots of butts too!
おっ お～！
おい 大蛇丸。
Hey, Orochimaru…
ん… 大蛇丸!?
Orochimaru?
この エロガキ！
You…pervy brat!
(自来也)アヂ～ッ！ アチッ アチッ アチッ。
Hot! Hot! Hot!
フフフッ。
熱湯はなしだろ アヂ～ッ！
Aw c'mon, hot water, really?!
Hot!
(自来也)作戦はこうじゃ。
This is the plan.
You disguise yourself and
make a move on Tsunade.
お前が変装して 綱手に絡む。
I'll appear just in time,
and chase you away.
すると わしが グッドタイミングで現れて
お前を追い払う。
すると綱手は 自来也君 すてき
となるわけだのぉ。
And Tsunade will say,
"Oh Jiraiya, you're so amazing!"
そんなことに
どんな意味があるの？
What's the point to all of this?
理解できない。
I don't understand it.
(自来也)
わしには意味があるんじゃ。
It has deep significance to me.
深～い意味がのぉ。
Very deep significance.
近いよ。
She's close by…
Huh?!
え？
(綱手)クソ～ あれだな
あのとき おりてたら…。
Damn it!
If…if only…I'd folded back then!
いや 賭けは
そんな簡単なことじゃない。
Nah…gambling isn't that simple.
あれは あれで あり。
That was that and…
ん… たぶん あり。 きっと あり。
Probably…
I'm sure...
ん～ そうね
あのときのスナップが…。
Yeah, it was the snap.
こう… サイコロの回転を…。
The way the dice rolled.
ここが勝負ってときにこそ
こう スナップが…。
That moment seals
whether you win or lose.
Yeah, the snap…
ん！ 何者だい？
Huh?!
Who are you?
(綱手)こっちは今 イライラしてんだ。
I'm in a bad mood right now.
(綱手)
ふざけたことすると 殺すぞ！
If you try anything…
I'll kill you!
うぉ～！
(大蛇丸)うわぁ～！
綱手！ だ 大丈夫かのぉ？
Tsunade!
A-Are you all right?
わしが来たからには…。
I'm here now, so…
もう… 安心…。
don't worry…
だ… のぉ。
Okay?
(綱手)はぁ？ なんでお前が
ここにいるんだい？
Huh? What're you doing here?
Actually… I mean, you see…
実はのぉ… いや その…。
今夜のお前は そこはかとなく
色っぽい… のぉ。
You're…looking…
awfully sexy…
tonight.
おい 自来也… 私は帰る。
Hey, Jiraiya…
I'm leaving.
アハハハハハ！
何してんだ？ お前たち。
Just what are you guys up to?
(自来也)フフフフフ… アハハハハ！
アハ… アハハハハ！
ヒヒヒヒヒ… エヘ…。
(綱手)さすがに
日が落ちると冷え込むな。
It gets so cold when night falls.
今夜は もう
やつらも襲ってこんだろう。
They won't attack us tonight.
なぁ！ 今宵は わしらの夢でも
語り合わんかのぉ？
Hey…
Why don't we talk about
our dreams tonight?
(大蛇丸)夢？
Dreams?
まぁ 夢があればの話だがのぉ。
If you have any dreams, that is.
(綱手)エロいことしか
頭にないと思ってたが…。
I thought all you only think
about is pervy stuff.
Jiraiya, it's an interesting topic
for you to bring up.
自来也！ 今夜は
おもしろいことを言うね。
(自来也)では 綱手から
話してもらおうかのぉ。
Well then, let's start with you, Tsunade.
私か？
Me?
私は この世界を
隅から隅まで見てみたい。
I want to see the world
from one corner to the other.
The world, you say?!
(自来也)世界とな！
大きく出たのぉ。
That's a bold dream!
フフッ！
世界のカジノで勝ちまくるのさ。
I'm going to win at
every casino there is!
で… お前の夢はなんなのさ？
So?
What's your dream?
うん わしの夢は…。
My dream is, perhaps…
世界を旅する綱手の
護衛でもするかのぉ。
to protect you during your travels.
(綱手)それは お断りするよ。
No thanks.
(自来也)大蛇丸 お前も たまには
自分のことを話さんかのぉ。
Orochimaru!
Open up and talk about yourself
once in a while.
(大蛇丸)夢…。
Dreams…
夢なんか ない。
(自来也)アハハハハ！
I don't have a dream.
おぬし ほんに つまらん男よのぉ。
You're such a boring guy.
(綱手)絡むな！
人はそれぞれだよ。
Leave him alone!
To each his own.
それに 話したくないことも…。
Besides, there are things
we want to keep to ourselves—
忍術を極めたい。
I want to master ninjutsu.
そして 誰よりも強くなる。
And become stronger than anyone.
(自来也)ほう… 何のためにじゃ？
Oh? For what purpose?
何のため？
For what purpose?
そんなこと 考えたこともないわ。
I've never thought
about such a thing.
なるほど… フン！ お前らしいのぉ。
I see…
That's so like you.
わかったようなことを言うわね。
Don't talk like you know me.
おぉ そうじゃ！
旅の見聞を書くのも いいのぉ。
Oh! I know!
Wouldn't it be great to write
about what we see and hear
綱手と世界を旅して…。
on our world travels, Tsunade?
お前は１人で行け！
You can go by yourself.
それは…。
That would be…
寂しい…。
so…
のぉ。
lonely.
うぉ～っ！
ハハハハハ！ おっ…。
はぁ～っ！
うぉ～っ！
(自来也)続々 来るのぉ。
(大蛇丸)あぁ。
They're coming one after another!
Yeah!
(綱手)ぶっ飛ばしてやる！
I'll pulverize them!
(カカシ)ああ そうか
これで最後ね。
Yeah…
This is the last.
いただきます。
Thank you for the food.
うん。
煮付けはもう極めたかな。
I think I've mastered
nitsuke dishes.
SIMMERED FISH [NITSUKE]
EVERYDAY RECIPES FOR FISH
次は ムニエルでしょ。
SIMMERED FISH [NITSUKE]
EVERYDAY RECIPES FOR FISH
I guess I'll try meuniere next.
いってきます。
I'm leaving.
ねぇねぇ
お父さん お父さん。
Hey, Dad… Dad!
しかたないな。
わ～い わ～い！
Oh well, sure, what the heck.
Yay…yay!
Isn't that nice?
ICHIRAKU RAMEN
This place is great!
(カカシ)え～い やっ！
(ヒルゼン)ふん！
(カカシ)うわ！
(ヒルゼン)カカシは すごいな。
Kakashi, you are terrific.
わしでも気を抜いたら
一本とられるかもしれん。
If I let my guard down
even for a moment,
I think you'd beat me.
(カカシ)どうも。
Thank you.
(リン)すごいよね カカシ君。
Isn't Kakashi great?
(オビト)あいつの父ちゃんも
天才忍者だからな。
Well, his dad is a genius.
何もしなくったって
才能あるんじゃね？
Even if he doesn't do anything,
he probably still has the skills.
まあ 俺はうちはだし
もちろん頑張るしさ。
Anyway, I'm an Uchiha.
I'll keep doing my best.
あいつさ
きっとムッツリスケベだぜ。
I bet he's…a closet pervert.
カカシ君 すごいね！
そうか？
You're great, Kakashi.
Think so?
いつも練習してるの？
本当すごいよ！
Do you practice all the time?
Seriously, you're amazing.
別に…
本は少し読んだかな。
Not really…
I kind of read a few books.
う～ん よし。
ULTIMATE TECHNIQUES
All right!
なんか なんかすげえ。
He's… He's kinda amazing.
Oh!
あ！
すげえ！
カカシ お前 すげえよ。
Amazing…
Kakashi, you're amazing!
出て来いよ 多めに作ったから。
Come on out.
I made a lot.
食べていけばいいでしょ。
So you might as well stay and eat.
エヘヘ！
バレちゃった。
You caught me!
ごめんなさい。
I'm sorry…
え？ え～！
(リン)ハッ！
(オビト)アハハ！
カカシ君って
１人で暮らしてるの？
So Kakashi, you live by yourself?
あれだな お前のあれ
ビュビュッてやるの おもしろいな。
Hey! That thing you do,
that "whoosh-whoosh" is great.
うん ビュビュッて すごいね。
Yeah…that "whoosh-whoosh."
It's amazing.
そうか？
Think so?
(オビト)かわいい。
(リン)カカシ君 これって？
It's so cute…
What is this, Kakashi?
(カカシ)川魚のムニエル カカシ風。
River fish meunière…
Kakashi-style.
(３人)いただきます！
– Thank you for the food!
カカシ君 これ すっごくおいしいよ。
Kakashi, this tastes really good!
お店で食べる料理みたい。
It's like the food you get
in a restaurant.
確かに。
Yeah, this is great!
お前 すげえよ。
You're amazing…
(カカシ)そうか。
お前 料理人になるのか？
Think so?
Are you gonna become a chef?
え？ そんなわけないでしょ。
Huh? I doubt it.
(オビト)それもそうか。
I guess not, huh?
いってきます。
I'm leaving.
お～い カカシ。
Hey, Kakashi!
ハァ ハァ…。
昨日のごちそう うまかったぜ。
The food last night was great!
本当に うまかったよ。
It was really delicious.
あっ ねぇ 聞いてる？
Hey, are you listening?
あぁ。
Yeah…
おっ ここ うまいんだぜ。
ICHIRAKU RAMEN
Hey, this place is good.
うまそう！
あ ちょちょ… おい 待てよ。
ICHIRAKU RAMEN
It's looks delicious. I wanna try it.
Hey, hold on!
今度 来ようぜ。
あぁ。
Let's go here next time.
Yeah.
(ガイ)カカシ君 僕と青春しないかい？
Kakashi…
Do you want to spend the springtime
of your youth with me?
青春？
Springtime of youth?
キミは
僕の永遠のライバルになる 運命の人。
You are my eternal rival…
My man of destiny!
はぁ。
さあ 勝負だ！
Come on.
Fight me!
(カカシ)それは 勘弁だな。
Sorry, no.
いくぞ！ うりゃ～！
Here I come!
うわっ！
(ガイ)瞬殺か… さすがだよ。
Instant kill…
A-Amazing.
我が永遠のライバル… さすが だ…。
My eternal rival is…amazing.
ただいま。
I'm home.
あ… そうか。
Oh yeah…
明日か。
It's tomorrow.
いってきます。
I'm leaving.
父さん。
Dad…
父さんは 仲間のために
掟を破ったんでしょ？
You broke the rules
for your friends' sake, right?
俺にも仲間ができたよ。
I've made friends too.
でも
俺は父さんみたいにはならない。
But I'll never be like you, Dad.
掟は守る。
I'll obey the rules.
父さん じゃあまた。
I'll see you later, Dad.
いってきます。
I'm leaving.
おはよう！ もう体はいいの？
'Morning!
Are you feeling better?
昨日 休んじゃうからさ。
You were absent yesterday and
カカシがいないと つまんねえよ。
そうか。
it's no fun
(ガイ)カカシ君！
この前はキミに敗れたが→
それは以前までのマイト・ガイだ。
生まれ変わったマイト・ガイは
決してキミに負けたりはしない！
顔 まだ腫れてるけど。
そうさ 青春に終わりはないのさ。
(カカシ)青春って…。
さあ 勝負だ！
(オビト)おっ！
(リン)カカシ君。
へぇ～ ガイもやるじゃん。
(ガイ)は～っ！
あっ。
カカシ いけいけ～！
カカシ君 ファイト！
(ガイ)せ… 青春の光は→
決して… 決して消えたりは
しないのです！
(カカシ)そうかもね。